// Array of questions with options and correct answers
const questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "What is the other name of Mohammad Ali Bogra Formula?",
  answer: "Constitutional Formula",
  options: [
    "New Law of Pakistan",
    "Pakistan Report",
    "Third Report",
    "Constitutional Formula"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 2,
  question: "Which kind of system of Government was introduced by the 1962 constitution?",
  answer: "Presidential",
  options: [
    "Autonomous",
    "Presidential",
    "Bicameral",
    "Confederate"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 3,
  question: "According to the 1973 constitution what is the term of the office of President?",
  answer: "5 years",
  options: [
    "6 years",
    "5 years",
    "4 years",
    "3 years"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 4,
  question: "Where is the biggest Salt Mine located in Pakistan?",
  answer: "Jhelum",
  options: [
    "Mangora",
    "Jhelum",
    "Sawat",
    "None of these"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 5,
  question: "Allama Muhammad Iqbal delivered his famous Allahabad Address in?",
  answer: "1930",
  options: [
    "1929",
    "1930",
    "1931",
    "1932"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "In which year did Syed Jamal-u-din Afghani die?",
  answer: "1897",
  options: [
    "1895",
    "1896",
    "1897",
    "1898"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "Who was the second Prime Minister of Pakistan?",
  answer: "Kh. Nazim-ud-Din",
  options: [
    "Ch Muhammad Ali",
    "Kh. Nazim-ud-Din",
    "Liaquat Ali Khan",
    "Feroze Khan Noon"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "The third largest city of Pakistan is?",
  answer: "Faisalabad",
  options: [
    "Faisalabad",
    "Rawalpindi",
    "Sialkot",
    "Hyderabad"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "The founder of All India Muslim League Nawab Salimullah Khan belonged to?",
  answer: "Dhaka",
  options: [
    "Madras",
    "Karachi",
    "Dhaka",
    "Delhi"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "Who inaugurated the State Bank of Pakistan?",
  answer: "Quaid-e-Azam",
  options: [
    "Quaid-e-Azam",
    "Malik Ghulam Muhammad",
    "Liaquat Ali Khan",
    "Allama Muhammad Iqbal"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 11,
  question: "Which country assisted Pakistan in the construction of the Sandak Project?",
  answer: "China",
  options: [
    "Iran",
    "Saudi Arabia",
    "Afghanistan",
    "China"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 12,
  question: "KRL Stands for?",
  answer: "Khan Research Laboratories",
  options: [
    "Khan Research Laboratories",
    "Kahuta Research Laboratories",
    "Karachi Research Laboratories",
    "None of them"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 13,
  question: "Pakistan tested its nuclear device on ____?",
  answer: "28th May 1998",
  options: [
    "28th May 1998",
    "26th May 1997",
    "28th June 1999",
    "27th July 1997"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 14,
  question: "Who was the first Muslim C-in-C of Air Force?",
  answer: "Air Marshal Asgher Khan",
  options: [
    "Air Marshal Asgher Khan",
    "Air Marshal Zafar Chahdhry",
    "Air Marshal Anwar Khan",
    "None of them"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 15,
  question: "In which of the following city is the headquarters of Punjab Rangers located?",
  answer: "Lahore",
  options: [
    "Karachi",
    "Lahore",
    "Multan",
    "Rawalpindi"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 16,
  question: "In which of the following city is Military College Jhelum located?",
  answer: "Sarai Alam Gir",
  options: [
    "Risalpur",
    "Islamabad",
    "Sarai Alam Gir",
    "Sargodha"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 17,
  question: "Pakistan Academy for Rural Development is situated in ____?",
  answer: "Peshawar",
  options: [
    "Chitral",
    "Peshawar",
    "Bannu",
    "Mardan"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 18,
  question: "Which mountain range separates Pakistan and Afghanistan?",
  answer: "The Hindu Kush",
  options: [
    "Karakoram range",
    "Pamirs Range",
    "The Hindu Kush",
    "Kirthar Range"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 19,
  question: "Archaeologists have identified some 400 Indus civilization towns, scattered from ____?",
  answer: "Kabul to Delhi",
  options: [
    "Kabul to Delhi",
    "Kabul to Lahore",
    "Peshawar to Delhi",
    "Kandhar to Delhi"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 20,
  question: "Manchar Lake is situated in ____?",
  answer: "Jamshoro",
  options: [
    "Larkana",
    "Dadu",
    "Thatta",
    "Jamshoro"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 21,
  question: "Lal Shahbaz Qalandar wrote several books in Persian and ____?",
  answer: "Arabic",
  options: [
    "Persian",
    "Arabic",
    "Sindhi",
    "Punjabi"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 22,
  question: "Which city of the Sindh is popular for woodwork industry?",
  answer: "Hala",
  options: [
    "Thattha",
    "Kotri",
    "Hala",
    "Larkana"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 23,
  question: "World Tuberculosis Day is observed on ____?",
  answer: "24th March",
  options: [
    "21st March",
    "24th March",
    "26th March",
    "25th March"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 24,
  question: "Name the range which separates China from Pakistan?",
  answer: "Karakoram",
  options: [
    "Hindu Kush",
    "Pamir",
    "Himalayas",
    "Karakoram"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 25,
  question: "What is the Height of Tirichmir peak?",
  answer: "7708 meters",
  options: [
    "7708 meters",
    "7350 meters",
    "7870 meters",
    "7140 meters"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 26,
  question: "What is the maximum height of Kirthar Range?",
  answer: "2150 meters",
  options: [
    "2150 meters",
    "2500 meters",
    "2375 meters",
    "2275 meters"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 27,
  question: "Which is the highest peak of Koh-e-Sulaiman range?",
  answer: "Takhat-e-Sulaiman",
  options: [
    "Tirichmir",
    "K-2",
    "Takhat-e-Sulaiman",
    "Sakar"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 28,
  question: "How many Peaks in Pakistan are higher than 7000 meters?",
  answer: "108",
  options: [
    "108",
    "117",
    "125",
    "191"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 29,
  question: "Golra Sharif is famous for the shrine of ____?",
  answer: "Pir Mehar Ali Shah",
  options: [
    "Pir Mehar Ali Shah",
    "Bari Imam",
    "Pir of Zakori",
    "Punj Pir"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 30,
  question: "Who was the first Prime Minister of Azad Kashmir?",
  answer: "Khan Abdul Hameed Khan",
  options: [
    "Sardar Muhammad Ibrahim Khan",
    "Khan Abdul Hameed Khan",
    "Sardar Sikandar Hayat Khan",
    "Moulana Muhammad Yousaf"
  ]
}
];
